One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The Hero Garp is...
protecting the platform!
Don't get intimidated. It's just a name, you fools!
He's just an old marine.
Since you're part of his generation,
you'd do well to pay attention to the enemy in front of you!
Crimson Dog Bite!
You keep destroying the city...
Like I said, try to protect it!
Monster
Make a path!
A path to Ace's rescue!
Those aggravating jerks came all the way here...
Not gonna happen, you monster!
We'll show you the power of the New World!
Now, hurry!
To the execution platform!
What is it, Fire Fist?
Ace...
Gol D. Roger?
You mean Gold Roger?
If I know him?
Hey, don't you know why there's so many pirates causing trouble in the world?
It's all that Roger-guy's fault!
Roger's...
This is just what I've heard...
but seems he spouted some crap about a
"great treasure" just before they executed him...
So generations of pirates stupid enough
to believe him started roaming the seas.
It'd be better if that guy was never born!
He's scum!
From the platform, before he died, he sent pirates out to sea to do whatever the hell they wanted!
He was trouble when he was alive, and he's even more so now that he's dead!
He's the worst trash in the world! Remember that!
Huh? What's wrong?
Why are you getting so upset?
Say, who are you anyway, you little runt?
What were you doing down in the village, Ace?
There's a huge uproar down there because some delinquents were almost killed by a kid.
What? And here I thought they were dead.
What?! When you cause trouble, I'm the one who gets blamed, you know!
You listening to me, Ace?!
Sheesh! How could he push
such a troublemaker on me?
You want to know about Roger, you say?
He was...
just a liar and a murderer!
"Pirate King"? Don't make me laugh!
He wasn't the Pirate King, more like the Bullshit King!
You can say that again!
Roger?
Don't say such disgusting
names, kid. You'll spoil my beer.
Get lost.
Why're you lookin' at me like that?!
Hey! What are you doing, you damn brat?!
Why are you looking so beat down?
Hey, Ace!
Looks like you've been causing a lot of trouble lately.
Gramps...
You have a grandson, right?
Does he seem happy to you?
Oh, you mean Luffy?
I'm raising him well.
Gramps.
Was it...
good that I was born?
Well, you...
As long as you're alive, you'll figure it out eventually.
Hurry and bring Straw Hat-boy to the ship!
Now that it's come to this, vwe'll just have to save Ace-boy vourselves!
Iva-chan...
Vyou're still conscious?!
I have one last favor to ask of you...
Just a little further! We're coming now, Ace!
Clear a path!
I'm...
Dammit!
Ace-san, wait for me! I will save you even if it costs me my life!
Almost there!
Here we come, Ace!
Ace! We'll definitely save you!
Wait for us, Ace!
Don't you dare give up!
Dammit! What's wrong with me?! This isn't the time to...
Pops, my brother and my crew...
are falling, and yet...
"One last favor"?! Don't say such ominous things!
Please, give me...
I'm so happy...
my tears won't stop...
Even now that it's come to this...
I want to live...
Captain Buggy, you're awake!
You're alive!
Thank goodness!
What happened to me?
You were frozen by that Aokiji-guy.
Oh no!
Hear me, Navy! You'd better prepare yourselves!
Don't think I'm the kind of man who'll let it end with this!
Yeah! We'll get our revenge before long! I'd expect no less from you!
Indeed, my friend!
But... what am I gonna do?!
Move it, Magma-brat!
Damn it to Hell...
Pops!
So even you can't fight old age, huh?
Whitebeard!
The one thing we'd feared the most...
You want me to wear this equipment so the enemy will feel sorry for me or something?!
Pops...
The battle is over once you let your guard down, even for a second!
Marco!
You just got distracted, didn't you?
Jozu!
Now, I guess it's time for me to send you off to the next world!
Pops!
Hey, Pops...
What?!
Vyou want another shot of the Tension Hormones?!
That's too reckless!
It's hopeless! Vyou and Vi fought our way out of Impel Down together, didn't vwe?!
Vyour body has been fatally poisoned and
then brought back from the brink of death...
It's way beyond its limits!
Didn't Vi tell you before? The Tension Hormones are nothing but an emergency treatment!
If Vi keep deceiving vyour body, vyou really will die after this is all over!
As long as I've done all I can,
then I don't mind dying!
Please let me fight, Iva-chan!
Pops was done in!
Marco! Jozu!
If... I don't fight here...
If... I can't save Ace...
I'll...
end up wanting to die!
Please... Give me the power to fight!
And Vi'm telling vyou...
If Vi allow vyou to die, Vi won't be able to show my face to Dragon afterwards!
Vyou ignorant fool!
Ace...
Fine!
Do whatever the hell...
vyou want!
Hey, you! What are you doing to Straw Hat?
S-Straw Hat's...
I-Impossible! I thought he was on the verge of death after taking Kizaru-san's attack head-on!
Luffy...
Ace!
Straw Hat-boy, once again, you better keep in mind...
that the next time you drop, you won't be able to bounce back!
Those guys!
Wait!
They're trying to execute Ace again!
Oh, well, my words can't change Straw Hat-boy's mind under these circumstances!
All I can do is keep them from beating him!
Straw Hat?!
Straw Hat is coming!
Kill Straw Hat!
I'm gonna finish him!
It's not over! I won't let you pass through here!
If you wanna advance...
You gotta beat all of us!
We'll show you the spirit of the Navy!
Heads up!
Death Wink!
10 points! I'll back you up!
Thanks, Ivan-chan!
Luffy-san...
Koby!
That's right! In order to
live as a Navy soldier,
I have to fight to change myself!
Because this is a battlefield!
I have to commit myself towards killing him!
Rubber-Rubber...
Shave!
Bullet!
He's as strong as I thought...
What is it this time?!
You guys are...
the Kuma imposters!
Monkey D. Luffy.
Oh no! What a pain in the ass!
Hey you, watch out!
Boa Hancock. One of the Seven Warlords.
Abort attack. Friendly operative.
That's right! You guys are on the same side!
Thank you, Hancock!
She's the Empress, right?
How do you know her?
Luffy! He called my name again...
Move aside, Boa Hancock.
I don't want you to call my name!
P-Pops...
I-I'm on my way!
You are off guard!
Pops!
Things don't always go the way you want!
Of course, Marco the Phoenix regenerates!
Hey! It's your turn now!
Seastone?!
Commander Marco!
It looks painful!
Commander Jozu has been beaten, too!
They even beat our commanders one by one...
The Whitebeard Pirates are falling apart...
Pops!
You Fishman monster!
Let me go!
Now move it!
Everyone, attack Whitebeard!
Pops!
Stay away!
These guys... do they really think...
they can beat me this easily?
I don't need any help because I'm...
I'm...
I'm Whitebeard!
M-Monster!
If I were to die...
I know exactly...
what it would mean!
Then, you know,
I can't allow myself to die until...
I see a bright future ahead for my sons!
Right, Ace?
Pops!
You just refuse to die!
What is it?!
W-What are they doing?!
Guarding the back of Whitebeard?!
Are they willing to die with Whitebeard?!
You people will never understand!
We'll defend Pops' glory!
You're getting too worked up, you fools!
If you wanna see the future,
I'll show you now, Whitebeard!
Do it!
Ace!
That won't work!
Do you really think that would stop...
Behold, Whitebeard!
Stop it!
Here I come!
What did vyou just do?!
Conqueror's... Haki?!
Hey, hey! Seriously?!
How surprising...
That kid...
Editing, Sewil
Quality Control, Galaxy 9000, Pepperjack
Timing, Sewil
Translation, Yibis/Funimation
Visual Effects, Datenshi, KaitouYahiko
Graphics, Datenshi
Karaoke, KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking, Halee
Raws, cloaknsmoke